[	{
		"question": "In HTML5, which tag or tags embed a webpage inside of a webpage?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "<iframe>, <frame>, and <frameset>",
			"choice2": "<frame>",
			"choice3": "<iframe>",
			"choice4": "`<frame> and <frameset>"
		},
		"correct": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the best way to apply bold styling to text?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "<strong>",
			"choice2": "Using CSS",
			"choice3": "<bold>",
			"choice4": "<b>"
		},
		"correct": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "When is the `<link>` tag used?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "when linking style sheets, JavaScript, and icons for mobile apps",
			"choice2": "when linking style sheets, favicons, and preloading assets",
			"choice3": "when linking style sheets and favicons",
			"choice4": "when linking style sheets, external URLs, and favicons"
		},
		"correct": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "With which tags is the `<source>` element associated?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "`<svg>, <picture>, <audio>, and <video>`",
			"choice2": "`<picture>, <audio>, and <video>`",
			"choice3": "It is interchangeable with the `src` attribute, so any element which uses `src` may use `<source>`",
			"choice4": "`<audio> and <video>`"
		},
		"correct": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "When should you use `<ol>` and `<ul>` elements?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "Use `<ul>` when you want a bulleted list and `<ol>` when you want a numbered list.",
			"choice2": "Use `<ul>` when you have a list of items in which the order of the items matters. Use `<ol>` when you have a list of items that could go in any order.",
			"choice3": "Use `<ol>` when you want a bulleted list and `<ul>` when you want a numbered list.",
			"choice4": "Use `<ol>` when you have a list of items in which the order of the items matters. Use `<ul>` when you have a list of items that could go in any order."
		},
		"correct": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the difference between the post and get methods in a form?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "post is used for sending information to the server. get is used for retrieving form information from the server.",
			"choice2": "get is used for sending information to the server. post is used for retrieving form information from the server.",
			"choice3": "With get, data is included in the form body when send to the server. With post, the data goes through the URL.",
			"choice4": "With post, data is included in the form body when send to the server. With get, the data goes through the URL."
		},
		"correct": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the difference between the `<div>` and `<span>` tags?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "`<div>` is used where a generic block-level tag is needed, while `<span>` is used where a generic inline tag is needed.",
			"choice2": "`<div>` is used for major divisions on a page, while `<span>` is used to span across columns.",
			"choice3": "`<div>` is the industry-standard default tag, but you could use `<span>` if you prefer.",
			"choice4": "`<div>` is used where a generic inline tag is needed, while `<span>` is used where a generic block-level tag is needed."
		},
		"correct": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the difference between the `<head>` and `<header>` tags in HTML?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "There is only one `<head>` tag per page, while there may be many `<header>` tags.",
			"choice2": "The `<head>` tag may contain CSS and Javascript links, while the `<header>` tag may contain headings and navigational links.",
			"choice3": "all of these answers",
			"choice4": "The `<head>` tag contains meta information, while the `<header>` tag contains navigation, logos, and other page identifying content."
		},
		"correct": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What does the `<label>` tag do?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "It labels webpages with important information.",
			"choice2": "It visually associates a text label with an interface element.",
			"choice3": "It visually labels from fields.",
			"choice4": "It programmatically associates a text label with an interface element."
		},
		"correct": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which statement is true about the defer attribute of the HTML script tag?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "The defer attribute can work synchronously.",
			"choice2": "The defer attribute works only with generators.",
			"choice3": "The defer attribute works only with promises.",
			"choice4": "The defer attribute will asynchronously load the scripts in order."
		},
		"correct": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "Which tag is the root element of an HTML document?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "<DOCTYPE html>",
			"choice2": "<html>",
			"choice3": "<body>",
			"choice4": "<root>"
		},
		"correct": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the purpose of the async keyword in a script tag?",
		"answer": {
			"choice1": "It will download the script from the server when resources allow.",
			"choice2": "It will run the script after HTML parsing is complete.",
			"choice3": "It makes the script run when the script is ready.",
			"choice4": "It pauses the parsing of HTML code while the script runs."
		},
		"correct": 2
	},
]
